

DARKO DIMOVSKI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER ♥ KARLOVAC, 47000, CROATIA **♦** 0992585733

• DETAILS •

Marmontova Aleja 20 Karlovac, 47000 Croatia 0992585733 darkodimovski57@gmail.com

LINKS

<u>Facebook</u>

Instagram

<u>Linkedin</u>

o SKILLS o

CSS

HTML5

React

JavaScript

Strapi.io

Next.js

Tailwind CSS

Chakra.ui

• HOBBIES •

Gaming, playing guitar, bike riding.

PROFILE

Hello, i'm a programmer focused to build exceptional digital experiences. I'm ambitious and passionate about front-end development, always staying focused and ready to accept new challenges. I'm a team player with positive attitude and i like to share and accept knowledge from others.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Help Desk Technician at Printec Croatia, Zagreb

July 2007 — April 2015

CS ATM Dispatcher at Printec Croatia, Zagreb

April 2015 — December 2020

Technical Team Leader at Printec Croatia

January 2021 — Present

EDUCATION

High School of Chemistry

March 2005

Algebra University

April 2021 — November 2021

Fron-end developer